[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All babies are born with a soft spot on the top of their heads. What is this called?", "correct_answer": "Fontanelle", "incorrect_answers": ["Raspberry", "Soft Spot", "Neurocranium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What of these members of the bear family is the largest?", "correct_answer": "Polar bear", "incorrect_answers": ["Black bear", "Panda", "Grizzly bear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "http://www.123facts.com/ is referred to as this.", "correct_answer": "URL", "incorrect_answers": ["TCP", "WAP", "USB"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who produced and directed the 1998 movie Psycho, which is a remake of the 1960 film directed by Alfred Hitchcock?", "correct_answer": "Gus Van Sant", "incorrect_answers": ["Roman Polanski", "Milos Forman", "Vince Vaughn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that singer June Carter worked side by side with Reese Witherspoon, who portrayed her in Walk the Line, helping the actress to perfect the role.", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "WWW, an abbreviation well known to Internet lovers, actually stands for what?", "correct_answer": "World Wide Web", "incorrect_answers": ["World Wild Web", "Windows World Wide", "Wonderful World of Web-casting"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first person to be crowned Czar of Russia?", "correct_answer": "Ivan the Terrible", "incorrect_answers": ["Nicholas III", "Alexander IV", "Mikhail Romanov"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What cat breed has very thick short fur, large round eyes, round head and chubby cheeks?", "correct_answer": "British Shorthair", "incorrect_answers": ["Colorpoint Shorthair", "Selkirk Rex", "European Shorthair"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Nicky, the CIA  technician in both The Bourne Identity  and The Bourne Supremacy?", "correct_answer": "Julia Stiles", "incorrect_answers": ["Helena Sturm", "Joan Allen", "Laura Dern"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Red-tailed Hawks are hunted in the USA because of their frequent attacks on domestic animals.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Disney movie contains these lines: Twinkle twinkle, little bat / How I wonder what youre at? / Up above the world you fly / Like a tea tray in the sky?", "correct_answer": "Alice in Wonderland", "incorrect_answers": ["Fantasia", "Robin Hood", "Dumbo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the 50th Academy Awards ceremony in 1978, this 1977 movie was the winner in the Best Picture category.", "correct_answer": "Annie Hall", "incorrect_answers": ["The Goodbye Girl", "Julia", "Star Wars"]}]